Among others:

• This demo enables you to paste VSM-JSON data and see the corresponding VSM-sentence.

• You can also export this VSM-sentence or vsm-box to for example a pure SVG image:
  a sharp, lightweight vector format.

• If you set a `delay ..` for like 3 seconds, and then click the `Download SVG` button,
  then you still have some time to go mouse-hover any connector you may want to have highlighted
  in the image, before the Save dialog appears.

• Checking the `✓ White box` option will remove the vsm-box border and background,
  resulting in an image that focuses on the VSM-sentence only.
  ◦ The `✓ auto-white` option will enable this by default when you click Download.
  ◦ You can disable this `auto-white` and `White box`, if you want to create an image that shows
    how a VSM-sentence appears in a curation interface, i.e. with a vsm-box border + background.

• For info on how to convert SVG to EMG (e.g. for Word or Google Docs), click the `EMF tips` link.
